Guide to the Inge Morath Photographs and Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1896-2001; Series I; 136.99; (550 boxes)
  - Color Transparencies
    - General Slides
      - Personal
        - Houses
          - Knoll house, undated; 2 (Box 504)
          - Knoll house tennis barn, undated (Box 504)
          - Stillman house, 1973 (Box 504)
        - Nature
          - Wild vines, 1974 July (Box 505)
          - Roses of Sackville West; blueberries, flowers, 1961-1990 (Box 505)
            1961-16, 1973-02
          - Birds, 1987 July (Box 505)
          - Animals: springer spaniels, peacocks, horses, squirrels, and a frog, 1978 (Box 505)
          - Bees and butterflies from Connecticut, 1973 (Box 505)
            1973-02
          - Florida animals, 1970 (Box 505)
          - Elephant "tea party", 1989 (Box 505)
            1989-14: Creation of Martha Clarke's Ballet with animals, "Endangered Species" in South Carolina and Connecticut.
        - Arts
          - Atalbot, sculptures, 1975 (Box 506)
          - Mixed artwork, 1957, undated (Box 506)
          - Vionnet, Madeleine: Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1974 (Box 506)
          - Xhosa jewelry, undated (Box 506)
          - Rehearsal shots of Ballet "Vienna Lusthaus" conceived and directed by Martha Clarke, 1986 (Box 506)
            1986-04
          - Studies of Nudes, 1973; 2 (Box 506)
        - General
          - Portraits, 1982, undated (Box 507)
          - People, 1965, 1995 (Box 507)
            1965-14
          - Miscellaneous, 1972-1981 (Box 507)
          - Wien-Sculptor-Lobau/Donau, Linz, Wachau, undated (Box 507)
          - Bellevue, 1981 (Box 507)
          - Special locations, 1996-1997 (Box 507)
          - Haidplatz (Tere): Car show, church, carnival fireworks, undated (Box 507)
          - Mixed images, 1974-1982, undated; 7 (Box 508)
          - 4 by 5 inches color negatives, sixteen negatives, [1998] (Box 508)
            Includes 2 prints
          - Black-and-white portfolio, 1954-1987; 5 (Box 509)
        - Family and Friends
          - Arthur Miller: Portraits (Box 509)
            Arthur Miller in Roxbury, Connecticut, and during travels, as well as with family, friends, and associates.
            - Color and black-and-white contact sheets, 1985-1986 (Box 510)
            - Roxbury, Columbia, Hout Bay, South Africa, 1965-1999; 4 (Box 510)
              1971-01, 1977-01, 1980-12, 1987-253
            - At home in Roxbury, Manhattan, Urbino, 1983-1992; 5 (Box 511)
              1983-34, 1988-07, 1987-253, 1988-073
          - Inge Morath: Portraits, 1957-1983 (Box 512)
            Images of clippings by or about Morath; and photographs of Morath taken by Arthur Miller. Includes Paris, 1957-15
          - "Great Austrian State Prize for photography," dupes, 1992 (Box 512)
          - Rebecca Miller (Box 512)
            - Rebecca Miller, 1962-1965; 4 (Box 512)
              1962-43, 1963-04, 1964-06, 1965-01, 1965-09
            - "Rebecca with Arthur", 1965 (Box 513)
            - "Young Rebecca", 1965-1972; 2 (Box 513)
              1965-08, 1966-07, 1967-01, 1971-01
            - "Personal: Rebecca", 1972-1974; 3 (Box 513)
              1988-323
          - Miller family, 1974-1989; 3 (Box 514)
          - "Arthur and Inge", circa 1980-1990 (Box 514)
          - "Fishers Island", 1970 (Box 514)
          - "Gone Fishing" (Box 514)
          - "A wedding, a graduation", 1974 June (Box 514)
          - "Wedding", 1981 (Box 514)
          - "The Pascal family", 1988 (Box 514)
            1988-01
          - "Miller Snapshots: Debra Winger, Ezra Swerslow, Jeremy Thomas", [1988] (Box 514)
          - Martha's Vineyard, 1984 August (Box 514)
        - Connecticut, 1960-1967; 2
          1967-01
          - Nature, woods, 1967 (Box 515)
          - Plants, flowers, 1967 (Box 515)
          - Winter, 1967; 2 (Box 515)
          - Washington, Roxbury, 1969-1970 (Box 515)
            1969-01, 1970-01
          - Houses, Mystic, Roxbury, 1970 (Box 516)
          - Avon, Washington, Salisbury, 1971 (Box 516)
            1971-01
          - Roxbury, Aerial views of estate, 1972 (Box 516)
          - Fall, Brooklyn, 1973 (Box 516)
          - Autumn, Shephaug River, Stonington, 1974 (Box 516)
            1974-01
          - Animals, ducks, horses, grocery store, Connecticut River, Apple Blossom Fair, 1974 (Box 516)
          - Essex, Clapp wedding, Rumsey Hall School, 1975 (Box 517)
            1975-01
          - Roxbury: winter, morels, gardens, 1977-1978 (Box 517)
            1977-01, 1978-01
          - Roxbury, 1985-1989 (Box 517)
            1989-01
          - Roxbury: winter/spring, 1990-1991 (Box 517)
            1990-01, 1991-01
          - Roxbury Pond, 1990-1995; 3 (Box 517)
            1990-01, 1994-01, 1995-01
          - German shepherd, 1992 (Box 517)
        - "Inge's funeral photos", undated; 2 (Box 518)
          A selection of Inge Morath's black-and-white photographic work
        - "Photos of Inge", undated (Box 518)
        - Mixed Photographs
          - Aerial of swimming pool, undated (Box 519)
          - Silo, 1971 (Box 519)
          - "Apollo II on TV, moonshot", 1969 (Box 519)
            1969-06
          - "Contemporary house", 1974 (Box 519)
          - "Paintings", 1974 April (Box 519)
          - Marsh Island, Maine, Harriet and William Coffin, 1974 (Box 519)
          - "Dishes, paintings, gifts", 1974 (Box 519)
          - "Kitchen dinner set-up", 1975 (Box 519)
          - Yard excavation, beaver and pond, 1995 (Box 519)
          - Mark Lammert, 1996 (Box 520)
          - Roses on table, hammock, 1997 (Box 520)
        - Insurance photos
          - Roxbury fire, 1983 (Box 520)
          - Insurance photos, 1972-1974; 2 (Box 520)
          - Insurance photos, 1972-1981; 4 (Box 521)
          - "Doublets", 1972 August (Box 522)
          - "Bresil-Amazone", 1972 August (Box 522)
          - "China valuables, assurances", 1974 March (Box 522)
          - "Painting-Liberman (Alexander)-assurances", 1974 March (Box 522)
          - "Roxbury Insurance", 1974 March (Box 522)
  - Personal and Family Photographs
    This series consists of personal and travel photographs of Morath and her family identified as personal photographs by the Inge Morath Foundation. Also included are some related awards, photograph albums, and memorabilia.
    - Family and Ancestry
      - Family, 1897-1977; 4 (Box 523)
      - "Meinen Liebsten...[Dankbarkeit?] ...Titti", 1930 (Box 523)
      - Old family photographs, copy prints, undated (Box 523)
      - Early years, Austria, 1920-1951; 2 (Box 523)
      - Herman Morath, undated (Box 523)
      - Werner Morath, 1940, undated (Box 523)
      - Letter and copy photographs from Werner Morath, 1977 (Box 523)
      - Family photographs, 1933-1971; 3 (Box 523)
      - Family photographs, 1979 (Box 524)
        1979-14
      - Titti, 1899-1992; 5 (Box 524)
        Includes black-and-white and color photographs, and correspondence.
      - "A few glimpses of Titti's 85th summer," includes photocopies, 1977-1987 (Box 524)
      - "Titti's 88th birthday, and other events in Roxbury", 1977-1989 (Box 524)
      - Family photographs, circa 1960 (Box 526)
      - 4 small pocket albums, circa 1970-1980 (Box 526)
      - Roxbury, black-and-white and color photographs, 1969-1996; 7 (Box 526)
      - Heinz Weber, note, 1996 (Box 526)
      - "Bella", 1975-1978 (Box 527)
      - Color prints, 1971-1985 (Box 527)
      - Color prints, 1985-1990; 3 (Box 527)
      - Inge and Arthur, 1964-1980; 4 (Box 528)
      - "Travel diary to Reno, Nevada, July 1960, Inge Morath", undated (Box 528)
        Typescript of diary. Cover includes label, "for Arthur" by an unidentified hand. Material does not include photographs, but found filed in family photographs.
      - Inge and Arthur in China, 1979 (Box 529)
        1979-01
      - Millers in Egypt, 1981 (Box 529)
      - Inge in Egypt, 1981 (Box 529)
      - Inge's Moscow opening, 1988 (Box 529)
      - Inge and Arthur in Russia, 1967-1985 (Box 529)
      - Inge and Arthur, 1962-1964; 3 (Box 538)
      - Woman looking through microscope, photograph, [1910-1920?] (Box 539)
      - Family ancestors, 1896-1901 (Box 539)
      - Photograph, [1889] December (Box 539)
      - Two girls, photograph, circa 1890-1910 (Box 539)
      - Titti and [Inge], 1936 (Box 539)
      - Inge and Arthur at event, color photograph album, 1990-2000 (Box 540)
      - Inge and Arthur, framed photograph, circa 1962 (Box 541)
      - Scrapbook, photograph album, 1922-1967 (Box 542)
    - Work and Travel
      - Tokyo, [1970] (Box 530)
        Consists of black-and-white and color photographs, as well as some correspondence.
      - St. Lucia, 1995 (Box 530)
      - Gallery events, 1999 (Box 530)
      - Rotterdam, 1997 (Box 530)
      - Oshkosh, Wisconsin, 1982-1987 (Box 530)
      - Danube trip, 1994 (Box 530)
      - "Société Imaginaire", 1992 August (Box 530)
      - "New York opening: Spain in the Fifties, Spanish Institute", 1994 October 24 (Box 530)
      - Cuba, color photographs, 2000 (Box 530)
      - Color photographs and letters, 1977-1994 (Box 530)
      - Arthur and Inge, 1994 (Box 530)
      - Stockholm, 1992, 1995 (Box 530)
      - Black-and-white photographs, 1999 (Box 530)
        1999-09
      - Color photographs, 1986-1999; 5 (Box 530)
      - St. Andrews, Scotland, 1993 (Box 531)
      - Vilnius, 1992 (Box 531)
      - Navalcán, award photographs, 1998 (Box 531)
      - "Universidade de Santiago de Compostela con los atentos saludos del Rector Dario Villanueva," color photograph of Inge, undated (Box 531)
      - "Renaissance Theatre, Berlin", 1994 (Box 531)
      - Berlin show opening, 1993 (Box 531)
      - Frankfurt show opening, 1994 (Box 531)
      - Germany, 1991 (Box 531)
      - Danube, 1993 (Box 531)
      - Inge and Arthur at Navalcan, color photograph album, undated (Box 531)
      - Tokyo, color photograph album, 1996 (Box 531)
      - Vienna, Austria, 1992; 5 (Box 531)
      - Various photographs of Inge Morath, 1970-1998; 5 (Box 531)
      - Madrid postcards, 1981 (Box 532)
      - Linz, 1992; 2 (Box 532)
      - Germany, Inge Morath show, 1991; 2 (Box 532)
      - Wien, 1999 (Box 532)
      - Photograph of Inge, brochure, "Mr. Arthur Miller," envelope with flower, 1992-1996 (Box 532)
      - Inge at show, circa 1990 (Box 532)
      - "The House Roxbury", 1988-1991 (Box 532)
      - [Salisbury], 1991 April (Box 532)
      - Cuba, 2000-2001 (Box 532)
      - Various photos of Inge Morath, 1993-2000 (Box 532)
      - Photo albums, 1927-1969; 4 (Box 533)
      - Photo album, circa 1999 (Box 534)
      - Framed photograph of Inge Morath, undated (Box 535)
      - "Rebecca," framed photograph, 1970-1980 (Box 535)
      - "Rebecca," framed photograph, 1984 (Box 535)
      - Framed photographs, undated (Box 535)
      - Ehrenmedaille der Bundeshauptstadt Wien, 1998 December 17 (Box 536)
      - National Arts Club, award, 1999 May 7 (Box 536)
      - Award in wooden box, undated (Box 536)
      - Inge in Uruguay, 1999 November (Box 537)
      - Film strip, photographic prints and letter, 1994 March (Box 537)
      - Argentina, 1993 (Box 537)
      - Graz and Leica Gallery opening, 1993-1995 (Box 537)
      - Inge and Arthur, panoramic color prints, [1990-2000] (Box 537)
      - Arthur and still lifes, color contact sheet, [1970?] (Box 537)
  - Collected Photographs
    This subseries consists of photographs of Morath by her friends and fellow photographers, including Henri Cartier-Bresson and Yul Brynner.
    - Photographs of Morath, 1930-1960; 3 (Box 543)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1950-1960; 4 (Box 543)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1956-1979; 2 (Box 543)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1952-1959; 9 (Box 544)
    - Photographs of Morath by Henri Cartier-Bresson, 1954-1963; 4 (Box 545)
    - Magnum Photos group photographs, 1990-1994 (Box 545)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1954-1997; 7 (Box 545)
    - Photographs of Morath, circa 1980 (Box 545)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1960-1986; 5 (Box 546)
    - "Portraits," Gotham Bookmart show opening, 1986 November 3 (Box 547)
    - Photographs of Morath by Elfriede Mejchar, Vienna, 1994 (Box 547)
    - Photographs of Morath, Austria, 2001 (Box 547)
    - Moscow Peace Forum, photographs by Sidney Geich, 1987 February (Box 547)
    - Forum, 1984 October (Box 547)
    - Moscow show opening, 1988 (Box 547)
    - Vienna, 1994 (Box 547)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1979-1992; 5 (Box 547)
    - Photographs of Morath by Henri Cartier-Bresson, 1960-1970; 2 (Box 548)
    - Magnum Photos group, 1950-1059 (Box 548)
    - Photographs of Morath by Christine de Grancy, 1992 (Box 548)
    - Photographs of Morath by Kerbler, 2001; 2 (Box 548)
    - Morath and work, 1984, undated (Box 548)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1950-1969; 3 (Box 549)
      1954-18, 1955-31, 1960-01, 1969-01
    - Photographs of Morath by Nikolaus Korab, Bengt Wanselius, Christine de Grancy, 1982-1992 (Box 549)
    - "Inge in Spain," and notes, 1955 (Box 549)
    - Photographs of Morath, 1961-1984; 4 (Box 549)
    - Roxbury, 1960-1990 (Box 549)
    - Photographs of Morath by Brigitte Lacombe, 1997 (Box 550)
    - Photographs of Morath by others, 1960-2001; 4 (Box 550)
- Papers, 1853-2012; Series II; 79.73; (141 boxes) + 7 broadsides, 1 roll; 79.73 linear feet (141 boxes) + 7 broadsides, 1 roll
  Series II is organized into seven subseries: Story Lists, Captions, Notebooks, General Files, Publicity, Project Files, and Awards.
  This series consists of papers that document the life and work of Inge Morath. It includes story captions, notebooks, correspondence, clippings, financial records, and awards.
  - Story Lists, undated, circa 1970
    The Story Lists describe the subjects of 775 of Morath's photographic projects arranged chronologically. They provide context for identifying photographic material created by her throughout the collection. Additionally, the Story Lists often document the number of rolls or negatives created for a project, as well as any lacking rolls. The Story Lists do not have information for stories created after 1991.
    See: Series I. Photographs.
    - Story List, undated (Box 551)
    - Story List, undated (Box 552)
    - Rolodex index to the Story List, circa 1970 (Box 553)
      Organized alphabetically by country
  - Captions, 1953-2001
    This subseries consists of the captions created by Morath that identify and describe individual images related to story numbers. The captions document her travel, projects, assignments, and subjects of interest. Depending on the story, the captions vary from brief to in-depth descriptions.
    Morath and other Magnum Photos photographers assigned chronological story numbers to their projects. These numbers consist of digits for the year of image creation, followed by a sequential number for the story (assignment, job, or project) within the given year, and then often by numbers that identify the roll and exposure frame. The captions for individual story numbers include descriptions from roll to roll and often from exposure frame to frame.
    The caption files for discrete story numbers may also contain related correspondence, essays, lists, notes, clippings, brochures, maps, and ephemera.
    The sets of captions include duplicates and photocopies. Story lists and indices often accompany captions and provide multiple story numbers for a specific year, which document story numbers Morath used for a single project.
    Notes in the guide for this group of material include descriptive inscriptions accompanying the captions.
    Organized under two headings: Personal Set and Magnum New York Set.
    Associated materials: A nearly complete representation of images described by the captions can be found in Series I. Photographs, Contact Sheets subseries.
    - Personal Set
      This material consists of Morath's personal set of captions.
      Arranged chronologically and sequentially by story number.
      - Max Ophüls, "To love a little more.. ." typescript by Inge Morath, [1953?] (Box 554)
      - 1953-01 to 1954-18 (Box 554)
        "List of stories in boxes"
      - 1953-01 to 1953-02 (Box 554)
      - 1953-03 (Box 554)
      - 1953-04 (Box 554)
      - 1953-07 (Box 554)
      - 1953-08 (Box 554)
      - 1953-11 (Box 554)
      - Copies of captions for exhibition prints, 1954 May (Box 554)
      - 1954-02 (Box 554)
      - 1954-03 (Box 554)
      - 1954-05 (Box 554)
      - 1954-06 (Box 554)
      - 1954-13 (Box 554)
      - 1954-16 (Box 554)
      - 1954-18, 4 (Box 554)
      - 1955-19 (Box 554)
      - 1955-21 (Box 554)
      - 1955-26 (Box 554)
      - 1955-31 (Box 554)
      - 1955-32 (Box 554)
      - 1955-33 (Box 554)
      - 1955-34 (Box 554)
      - 1955-35 (Box 554)
      - 1955-36 (Box 554)
      - 1956-09, 2 (Box 554)
      - 1956-10, 5 (Box 555)
      - 1956-11 (Box 555)
      - 1956-12, 1956-23, 1957-07, 1957-12, 1956-1957 (Box 555)
        "Spanish stories continued"
      - 1956-19 (Box 555)
      - 1957-02 (Box 555)
      - 1957-04 (Box 555)
      - 1957-07 (Box 555)
      - 1957-10 (Box 555)
      - 1957-12 (Box 555)
      - 1958-03 (Box 555)
      - 1958-05 (Box 555)
      - 1958-06 (Box 555)
      - 1958-07 (Box 555)
      - 1958-09, 1958-15 (Box 555)
        Romania: "Rumania captions color selection in Magnum," set.
      - 1958-14 (Box 555)
      - 1958-16 (Box 555)
      - 1958-17 (Box 555)
      - 1958-18 (Box 555)
      - 1959-01 (Box 555)
      - 1959-03 (Box 555)
      - 1959-04 (Box 555)
      - 1959-05 (Box 555)
      - 1959-06 (Box 555)
      - 1959-07 (Box 555)
      - 1959-18 (Box 555)
      - 1959-26 (Box 555)
      - 1959-31 (Box 555)
      - 1960-01 (Box 555)
      - 1960-04 (Box 555)
      - 1960-05 (Box 555)
      - 1960-08 (Box 555)
      - 1960-15 (Box 555)
      - 1960-16 (Box 556)
      - 1960-21 (Box 556)
      - 1960-24 (Box 556)
      - 1961-10 (Box 556)
      - 1961-11 (Box 556)
      - 1961-16 (Box 556)
      - "Les Royaumes Berberes," chapter VI, typescript, circa 1961 (Box 556)
      - 1961-18 (Box 556)
      - 1961-28 (Box 556)
      - 1961-32 (Box 556)
      - 1962-15 (Box 556)
      - 1962-17 (Box 556)
      - 1965-01 (Box 556)
      - 1965-05 (Box 556)
      - 1965-08 (Box 556)
      - 1965-09 (Box 556)
      - 1965-10 (Box 556)
      - 1965-15 (Box 556)
      - 1965-16 (Box 556)
      - 1965-17 (Box 556)
      - 1966-08 (Box 556)
      - 1966-10 (Box 556)
      - 1967-04 (Box 556)
      - 1967-11 (Box 556)
      - 1968-01 (Box 556)
      - 1968-04 (Box 556)
      - 1969-01 (Box 557)
      - 1969-02 (Box 557)
      - 1969-03 (Box 557)
      - 1969-04 (Box 557)
      - 1969-05 (Box 557)
      - 1969-06 (Box 557)
      - 1969-08 (Box 557)
      - Caption notebook, circa 1970 (Box 557)
      - 1970-01 (Box 557)
      - 1970-03 (Box 557)
      - 1970-04 (Box 557)
      - 1970-05 (Box 557)
      - 1970-07 (Box 557)
      - 1970-08 (Box 557)
      - 1970-13 (Box 557)
      - 1971-01 (Box 557)
      - 1971-01 to 1971-05 (Box 557)
      - 1972-01 (Box 557)
      - 1972-02 (Box 557)
      - 1973-01 to 1973-14 (Box 557)
      - 1974-01 to 1974-20 (Box 557)
      - Correspondence and papers, 1975; 3 (Box 557)
      - 1975-01 (Box 557)
      - 1975-04 (Box 557)
      - 1975-07 (Box 557)
      - 1975-09 (Box 557)
      - 1975-10 (Box 557)
      - 1975-12 (Box 557)
      - 1975-13 (Box 557)
      - 1975-15 (Box 557)
      - 1976-01 to 1976-17 (Box 557)
      - 1976-02 (Box 557)
      - 1976-08 (Box 557)
      - 1976-11 (Box 557)
      - 1977-01 (Box 557)
      - 1977-02 (Box 557)
      - 1977-03 to 1977-06 (Box 557)
      - 1977-09 (Box 557)
      - 1977-10 (Box 557)
      - 1977-11 (Box 558)
      - 1977-12 (Box 558)
      - 1977-14 (Box 558)
      - 1977-15 (Box 558)
      - 1977-16 (Box 558)
      - 1977-18 (Box 558)
      - 1977-20 (Box 558)
      - 1977-21 (Box 558)
      - 1978-01 (Box 558)
      - 1978-05 (Box 558)
      - 1978-10 (Box 558)
      - 1978-12, 2 (Box 558)
        China I and "Chinese Encounters," book
      - 1979-04 (Box 558)
      - 1979-05 to 1979-51, 3 (Box 558)
        China II, and "captions used for the Grand Rapids Art Museum show, 1979 October 15."
      - 1979-16 (Box 558)
      - 1980-01 (Box 558)
      - 1980-05 (Box 558)
      - 1980-06 (Box 558)
      - 1980-07 (Box 558)
      - 1980-09 (Box 558)
      - 1981-02, 2 (Box 558)
      - 1981-05 (Box 558)
      - 1982-02 (Box 558)
      - 1982-10 (Box 559)
      - 1983-02 (Box 559)
      - 1983-09 (Box 559)
      - 1983-18 (Box 559)
      - 1983-19 (Box 559)
      - 1984-10 (Box 559)
      - 1985-02 (Box 559)
      - 1985-14 (Box 559)
      - 1986-01 (Box 559)
      - 1986-02 (Box 559)
      - 1986-03 (Box 559)
      - 1986-04 (Box 559)
      - 1986-08 (Box 559)
      - 1986-13 (Box 559)
      - 1987-01 (Box 559)
      - 1987-02 (Box 559)
      - 1987-06 (Box 559)
      - 1987-07 (Box 559)
      - 1987-13 (Box 559)
      - 1987-18 (Box 559)
      - 1987-21 (Box 559)
      - 1987-26 (Box 559)
      - 1987-27 (Box 559)
      - 1988-02 (Box 559)
      - 1988-05 (Box 559)
      - 1988-06 (Box 559)
      - 1988-07 (Box 559)
      - 1988-14 (Box 559)
      - 1988-15 (Box 559)
      - 1988-18 (Box 559)
      - 1989-02 (Box 559)
      - 1989-03 (Box 559)
      - 1989-04 (Box 559)
      - 1989-10 (Box 559)
      - 1989-11 (Box 559)
      - 1989-12 (Box 559)
      - 1989-17 (Box 559)
      - 1989-18 (Box 559)
      - 1990-04 (Box 559)
      - 1990-09 (Box 559)
      - 1990-10 (Box 559)
      - 1990-14 (Box 559)
      - 1991-02 (Box 559)
      - 1991-03 (Box 559)
      - 1992-02 (Box 560)
      - 1992-04 (Box 560)
      - 1992-05 (Box 560)
      - 1992-06 (Box 560)
      - 1992-07 (Box 560)
      - "Numbers of the Spanish stories for which I need contact sheets", 1993 (Box 560)
      - 1993-02 (Box 560)
      - 1993-03 (Box 560)
      - 1993-06 (Box 560)
      - 1993-07 (Box 560)
      - 1993-08 (Box 560)
      - 1993-09 (Box 560)
      - 1993-10 (Box 560)
      - 1993-11 (Box 560)
      - 1994-01 (Box 560)
      - 1994-02 (Box 560)
      - 1994-05 (Box 560)
      - 1994-09 (Box 560)
      - 1994-12 (Box 560)
      - 1994-14 (Box 560)
      - 1995-01 (Box 560)
      - 1995-03 to 1995-10 (Box 560)
        "Kaplan Show"
      - 1995-05 (Box 560)
      - 1995-07 (Box 560)
      - 1995-08 (Box 560)
      - 1995-09 (Box 560)
      - 1995-10 (Box 560)
      - 1995-11 (Box 560)
      - 1995-12 (Box 560)
      - 1995-13 (Box 560)
      - 1995-14 (Box 560)
      - 1995-17 (Box 560)
      - 1995-18 (Box 560)
      - 1996-03 (Box 560)
      - 1996-05 (Box 560)
      - 1996-06 (Box 560)
      - 1996-07 (Box 560)
      - 1996-08 (Box 560)
      - 1996-09 (Box 560)
      - 1996-10 (Box 560)
      - 1996-11 (Box 560)
      - 1996-15 (Box 560)
      - 1996-16 (Box 560)
      - 1997-01 (Box 560)
      - 1997-03 (Box 560)
      - 1997-04 (Box 560)
      - 2000-09 (Box 560)
      - 2001-03 (Box 560)
      - 2001-04 (Box 560)
      - 2001-05 (Box 560)
      - 2001-07 (Box 560)
    - Magnum New York Set
      This material consists of captions originally held by the office of Magnum Photos in New York City and reflect the editorial practice of the photographic cooperative. The captions possess Magnum Photos distribution numbers, which replicate the story numbers, except that the letter "D" or phrase "Magnum Distribution" precedes each number.
      - 1953-01 (Box 561)
      - 1953-02 (Box 561)
      - 1953-03 (Box 561)
      - 1953-04 (Box 561)
      - 1953-05 to 1953-07, story list (Box 561)
      - 1953-07 (Box 561)
      - 1953-08 (Box 561)
      - 1953-11 (Box 561)
      - 1954-01 (Box 561)
      - 1954-03 (Box 561)
      - 1954-05 (Box 561)
      - 1954-06 (Box 561)
      - 1954-07 (Box 561)
      - 1954-10 (Box 561)
      - 1954-11 (Box 561)
      - 1954-12 (Box 561)
      - 1954-13 (Box 561)
      - 1954-14 (Box 561)
      - 1954-15 (Box 561)
      - 1954-16 (Box 561)
      - 1954-17 (Box 561)